By Meiko Kawakami.
Here we have ...
Here we can accompany Natsuko and her sister and niece.
All these three women are in the middle of one of their own female thoughts.
There is a lot of breast enlargements talking about if her sister wants to do.
Natsuki himself is thinking about sperm donation.
Her niece, now I don't remember what her name is,
But she thinks very much about the first period she has not yet received.
What I think is very good about this book.
It is very long, but what is good about this book is how
This female perspective may arrive.
Kawakami, she like, she doesn't excuse anything.
She is not trying to beautify anything, but this is straightforward
About what many women go through.
And I love the liberating feeling of talking about the women's body in such a normal way.
So these things that a women's body goes through with the thoughts
without being objectified.
I gave it a strong four.
I thought it was a little too long.
Life after life by Kate Atkinson.
It feels so unusual to get up here, but I hope you keep up.
It just feels so strange to get up.
Life by life.
It was this.
This is a “dust off”
But this is also randomly chosen this for April.
So two flies in a bang with this book.
I was overjoyed.
You who saw the video for my TBR for April
Know how overjoyed I was about reading this one.
I was definitely not disappointed.
I made a reading logo.
I link the reading logging down in the description
so you can get to follow the trip as I read through it
When they mashed up and then they broke in.
Something happened and then you have to follow different characters.
How the memory also works.
I thought she succeeded very well with this.
There are so many who have said it is so good
Because you forget that this is an inventory.
This band does not exist.
This has never happened.
But she writes like it has actually happened.
I think it was very fascinating.
I gave a strong four.
I liked it just because I don't like rock.
But I didn't know it before.
Kara Thomas thinks her name feels familiar.
But I haven't read any of her.
We have to come along this.
Three friends who skip prom.
This is a youth book.
Mystery thriller for young people.
They skip their ball.
Student bale
And goes out to one of the friends' cabin.
And is there.
And should camp.
This is how something happens.
One of them is found but she has no memory of what has happened over the weekend
We have to follow her perspective.
How she tries to navigate.
What happened.
What went wrong.
What has happened to my friends.
and
He didn't disappoint me.
I was talking about
The Devil and the Darkwater
by Stuart Turton.
It is he who has written the seven
The fashion of Evelyn Hardcastle.
This puzzle covers with a sci-fi
Twist.
Everything with that book
I love.
It became a full point.
I do not know
I just died when I read that book.
I love it.
So it is, it's almost like that